<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?>

<ExcludedBuiltInGroups>
    <Group Sid="S-1-1-0" Name="Everyone" Excluded="true">
        A group that includes all users, even anonymous users and
        guests. Membership is controlled by the operating system
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-2" Name="Local Authority" Excluded="true">An identifier authority</Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-3" Name="Creator Authority" Excluded="true">An identifier authority.</Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-3-0" Name="Creator Owner" Excluded="true">
        A placeholder in an inheritable access control entry
        (ACE). When the ACE is inherited, the system replaces this SID with the SID for the object's creator.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-3-1" Name="Creator Group" Excluded="true">
        A placeholder in an inheritable ACE. When the ACE is
        inherited, the system replaces this SID with the SID for the primary group of the object's creator. The primary
        group is used only by the POSIX subsystem.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-3-2" Name="Creator Owner Server" Excluded="true"></Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-3-3" Name="Creator Group Server" Excluded="true"></Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-3-4" Name="Owner Rights" Excluded="true">
        A group that represents the current owner of the object.
        When an ACE that carries this SID is applied to an object, the system ignores the implicit READ_CONTROL and
        WRITE_DAC permissions for the object owner.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-4" Name="Non-unique Authority" Excluded="true">An identifier authority.</Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5" Name="NT Authority" Excluded="true">An identifier authority.</Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-1" Name="Dialup" Excluded="true">
        A group that includes all users who have logged on through a
        dial-up connection. Membership is controlled by the operating system.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-2" Name="Network" Excluded="true">
        A group that includes all users that have logged on through a
        network connection. Membership is controlled by the operating system.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-3" Name="Batch" Excluded="true">
        A group that includes all users that have logged on through a
        batch queue facility. Membership is controlled by the operating system.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-4" Name="Interactive" Excluded="true">
        A group that includes all users that have logged on
        interactively. Membership is controlled by the operating system.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-6" Name="Service" Excluded="true">
        A group that includes all users that have logged on
        interactively. Membership is controlled by the operating system.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-7" Name="Anonymous" Excluded="true">
        A group that includes all users that have logged on
        anonymously. Membership is controlled by the operating system.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-11" Name="Authenticated Users" Excluded="true">
        A group that includes all users whose identities
        were authenticated when they logged on. Membership is controlled by the operating system.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-18" Name="Local System" Excluded="true">
        A service account that is used by the operating system.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-19" Name="NT Authority" Excluded="true">Local Service.</Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-20" Name="NT Authority" Excluded="true">Network Service.</Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-32-544" Name="Administrators" Excluded="true">
        A built-in group. After the initial installation of
        the operating system, the only member of the group is the Administrator account. When a computer joins a domain,
        the Domain Admins group is added to the Administrators group. When a server becomes a domain controller, the
        Enterprise Admins group also is added to the Administrators group.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-32-545" Name="Users" Excluded="true">
        A built-in group. After the initial installation of the
        operating system, the only member is the Authenticated Users group. When a computer joins a domain, the Domain
        Users group is added to the Users group on the computer.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-32-546" Name="Guests" Excluded="true">
        A built-in group. By default, the only member is the Guest
        account. The Guests group allows occasional or one-time users to log on with limited privileges to a computer's
        built-in Guest account.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-32-547" Name="Power Users" Excluded="true">
        A built-in group. By default, the group has no members.
        Power users can create local users and groups; modify and delete accounts that they have created; and remove
        users from the Power Users, Users, and Guests groups. Power users also can install programs; create, manage, and
        delete local printers; and create and delete file shares.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-32-548" Name="Account Operators" Excluded="true">
        A built-in group that exists only on domain
        controllers. By default, the group has no members. By default, Account Operators have permission to create,
        modify, and delete accounts for users, groups, and computers in all containers and organizational units of
        Active Directory except the Builtin container and the Domain Controllers OU. Account Operators do not have
        permission to modify the Administrators and Domain Admins groups, nor do they have permission to modify the
        accounts for members of those groups.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-32-549" Name="Server Operators" Excluded="true">
        A built-in group that exists only on domain
        controllers. By default, the group has no members. Server Operators can log on to a server interactively; create
        and delete network shares; start and stop services; back up and restore files; format the hard disk of the
        computer; and shut down the computer.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-32-550" Name="Print Operators" Excluded="true">
        A built-in group that exists only on domain
        controllers. By default, the only member is the Domain Users group. Print Operators can manage printers and
        document queues.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-32-551" Name="Backup Operators" Excluded="true">
        A built-in group. By default, the group has no
        members. Backup Operators can back up and restore all files on a computer, regardless of the permissions that
        protect those files. Backup Operators also can log on to the computer and shut it down.
    </Group>
    <Group Sid="S-1-5-32-552" Name="Replicators" Excluded="true">
        A built-in group that is used by the File Replication
        service on domain controllers. By default, the group has no members. Do not add users to this group.
    </Group>
</ExcludedBuiltInGroups>